Pitt Jazz Collection, 1971-2011 UA.90.8.26.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Nathan Davis, 1973-2001; V.
  - Compositions
    - Just Above My Head Musical Score, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Just Above My Head, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Just Above My Head news clippings, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Just Above My Head Planning and Budget, 1987-2003 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Just Above My Head Promotional Material, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Just Above My Head Score Oboe 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Just Above My Head Score Oboe 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Just Above My Head Score Clarinet 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Just Above My Head Clarinet, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Clarinet 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Just Above My Head-Contrabass, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Just Above My Head-Trombone 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trombone 3, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Flute 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Flute 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Viola 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Viola 2 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Cello 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Cello 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trumpet 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Violin 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Violin 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Just Above My Head-Bassoon 1 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Just Above My Head-Bassoon 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Timpani, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Horn 1, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Horn 2 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Horn 3, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Horn 4 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trumpet 2 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trumpet 3, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trumpet 4 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trombone 2, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Just Above My Head Score-Trombone 4, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Kings on the Hill Film Score, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Kings on the Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - A Beacon of Light, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Happy Girl, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Saxaphone Sheet Music, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Flute, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Violin, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Bassoon, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Trumpet, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Clarinet, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Oboe, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Percussion, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-French Horn, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Harp, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Viola, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Cello, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Contrabass, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Trombone, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Concerto No. 1 in C Minor-Jazz Piano and Orchestra (Box 46)
    - Nathan Davis Sheet Music, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 100)
- Geri Allen
  - Geri Allen Jazz Times Article, September 2013 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Photographic Material, ca. 1971-1998, undated; VI.
  The Nathan Davis photographs are largely images used in two of his publications, Jazz Seminar Photo Album and Writings in Jazz. The series also contains publicity shots, candid images of Dr. Davis and related topical photographs.
  - Pitt Jazz Seminar and Concert, 1971-2000; 1.
    - Publicity Shots: Monty Alexander, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Publicity Shots: Benny Bailey, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Publicity Shots: David Baker, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Publicity Shots: Kenny Barron, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Publicity Shots: Oscar Brashear, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Publicity Shots: Randy Brecker, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Publicity Shots: Donald Byrd, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Publicity Shots: Terri Lyne Carrington, ca. 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Publicity Shots: Ron Carter, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Publicity Shots: George Cables, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Publicity Shots: Harry Connick Jr., ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Publicity Shots: Hank Crawford, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Publicity Shots: Alan Dawson, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Publicity Shots: Ray Drummond, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Publicity Shots: Kevin Eubanks, ca. 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Publicity Shots: Jon Faddis, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Publicity Shots: Eddie Gomez, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Publicity Shots: Winard Harper, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Publicity Shots: Eddie Henderson, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Publicity Shots:Terumasa Hino, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Publicity Shots: Freddie Hubbard, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Publicity Shots: Johnny Griffin, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Publicity Shots: Milton Jackson, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Publicity Shots: Illinois Jacquet, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Publicity Shots: Elvin Jones, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Publicity Shots: Abraham Laboriel, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Publicity Shots: Russell Malone, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Publicity Shots: Herbie Mann, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Publicity Shots: Jackie McLean, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Publicity Shots: Maracio Montarroyos, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Publicity Shots: Mulgrew Miller, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Publicity Shots: Johnny Griffin, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Publicity Shots: T.S. Monk, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Publicity Shots: James Moody, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Publicity Shots: Michael Mossman, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Publicity Shots: Jimmy Owens, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Publicity Shots: John Patitucci, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Publicity Shots: Emily Remler, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Publicity Shots: Sonny Rollins, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Publicity Shots: Wallace Roney, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Publicity Shots: Patrice Rushen, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Publicity Shots: Arturo Sandoval, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Publicity Shots: John Scofield, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Publicity Shots: Akira Tana, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Publicity Shots: Billy Taylor, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Publicity Shots: Stanley Turrentine, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Publicity Shots: Ernie Watts, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Publicity Shots: Freddie Waits, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Publicity Shots: Cedar Walton, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Publicity Shots: Grover Washington Jr., ca. 1979-1999 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Publicity Shots: Phillip Woo, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Publicity Shots: Attila Zoller, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - 1st-9th Annual Concert, 1971-1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 3rd Annual Concert, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - 5th Annual Concert, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - 6th Annual Concert, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - 7th Annual Concert, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - 10th-17th Annual Concert, 1980-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 11th Annual Concert Roll 1, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - 11th Annual Concert Roll 1 Negatives, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - 11th Annual Concert Roll 2, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - 11th Annual Concert Roll 2 Negatives, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - 13th Annual Concert, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - 13th Annual Concert, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 15th-18th Annual Concert, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - 20th-22nd Annual Concert, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 20th Annual Concert, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - 22nd Annual Concert, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - 22nd Annual Concert, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 23rd Annual Concert, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - 24th Annual Concert, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - 26th Annual Concert Rehearsal, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 113-114)
    - 27th Annual Concert Rehearsal, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - 27th Annual Concert, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 115-116)
    - Donald Byrd, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - George Cables, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ron Carter, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Kenny Clarke, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - George Coleman, undated (Box 5, Folder 4B)
    - Jon Faddis, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Eddie Gomez, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5B)
    - Johnny Griffin, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Eddie Harris, undated (Box 5, Folder 6B)
    - Jimmy Heath, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Milt Jackson, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Mulgrew Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Joe Sample, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Marvin Smith, undated (Box 5, Folder 10B)
    - Clark Terry, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Grover Washington, Jr., c. 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Mary Lou Williams, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Jazz Seminar Outreach Program Pictures, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - General Photographs, ca. 1971-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 12th Annual Concert, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - 17th Annual Concert, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 69-70)
    - 28th Annual Concert Rehearsal, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - 30th Annual Jazz Seminar, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - 31st Annual Concert, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - 38th Annual Jazz Seminar, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 74-75)
    - 39th Annual Jazz Seminar, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 76-77)
    - 40th Annual Jazz Seminar, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 78-79)
    - 42nd Annual Concert, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 80-81)
    - 43rd Annual Concert, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 82-83)
    - 44th Annual Concert, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 84-85)
    - 45th Annual Concert, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 86-87)
  - International Academy of Jazz Hall of Fame, 1992, undated; 2.
    - Plaque, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Artifacts, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photo Op, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Inductee Bronze Busts (Negatives), Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Exhibit Space (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
  - International Jazz Archives Journal, 1993-1998, undated; 3.
    - Inaugural Journal Presentation, 1993-1998, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Duke Ellington and Billy Strayhorn, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Journal Volume 2 Number 1: Dionizy Piatkowski Photographs, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Jazz Studies at the University of Pittsburgh, ca. 1971-1998; 4.
    - University of Pittsburgh Jazz Ensemble, ca. 1971-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26-28)
  - Nathan Davis, ca. 1969-2000; 5.
    - Just Above My Head Premiere, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Portraits and Photographs, ca. 1969-2001 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
    - Nathan Davis, 1970-1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Nathan Davis (2), 1970-1990s (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Mellon Jazz Festival, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Photographic Credits, The University of Pittsburgh Jazz Seminar Photo Album Preface- Chapter 22, ca. 1971-1994 (Box 5, Folder 32-54)
    - Photographic Credits, The University of Pittsburgh Jazz Seminar Photo Album Chapter 23-Conclusion, ca. 1970-1994 (Box 5, Folder 55-57)
    - Jazz Seminar Photo Album Contact Sheets, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Jazz Seminar Photo Album Negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Photographic Credits, Writings in Jazz -5th Edition, ca. 1996 (Box 5, Folder 60-66)
    - Pittsburgh Jazz Artists, ca. 1971-2001 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Duke Ellington and Herb Douglas (Autographed), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Photographs from Unknown Events, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified Musicians, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified Commitee Members, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Audio/Video Material, 1973-1999; VII.
  - Audio Recordings, Pitt Jazz Seminar and Concert, 1973-1999; 1.
    - 3rd Annual Seminar, 1973
      - Gospel Concert with The Celestial Singers of Howard University, 1973 (Box 7, Reel 1-2)
      - 3rd Annual Concert, 1973 (Box 7, Reel 3-4)
    - 4th Annual Seminar, 1974
      - Keyboard Workshop with Jaki Byard | Improvising Workshop with Tom McIntosh, 1974 (Box 9, Reel 1)
      - Unknown Jazz Seminar Material, 1974 (Box 9, Reel 2)
      - 4th Annual Concert, 1974 (Box 7, Reel 5-6)
    - 5th Annual Seminar, 1975
      - Unknown Material, 1975 (Box 7, Reel 7)
      - Unknown Material, 1975; 3. (Box 9, Reel 3)
    - 6th Annual Seminar, 1976
      - Jazz Films and Lecture With Leonard Goines, 1976 (Box 9, Reel 4)
      - Arrangement and Composition Workshop with Don Sebesky, 1976 (Box 9, Reel 5)
      - Brass Workshop with Clark Terry and Guitar/Harmonica Workshop with Toots Thielmans, 1976 (Box 9, Reel 6)
      - Rhythm Section Workshop with Max Roach, Terry Pollard, and Abraham Laboriel. Saxophone Session with Jimmy Heath Part I., 1976 (Box 9, Reel 7)
      - Saxophone Workshop with Jimmy Heath Part II., 1976 (Box 9, Reel 8)
      - 6th Annual Concert, 1976 (Box 9, Reel 9-10)
    - 7th Annual Seminar, 1977
      - History and Evolution of the Music Industry with George Butler | Arranging Workshop with Phill Rizzo, 1977 (Box 9, Reel 11)
      - Gospel Concert with Bobbie and Bobby Fulton, 1977 (Box 9, Reel 12)
      - Reeds Workshop with Dexter Gordon, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 9-10)
      - Brass Workshop with Woody Shaw, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 11)
      - Drums Workshop with Kenny Clarke, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 12)
      - 7th Annual Concert, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 13-18)
    - 8th Annual Seminar, 1978
      - 8th Annual Concert, 1978 (Box 9, Reel 13-19)
    - 10th Annual Seminar, 1980
      - Workshop with Donald Byrd, 1980 (Box 20-22)
      - Gospel Concert with the Kentucky State University Gospel Choir and Patrick Roache and the Sounds of Love, 1980 (Box 10, Reel 1-3)
      - 10th Annual Concert, 1980 (Box 10, Reel 4-6)
    - 11th Annual Seminar, 1981
      - 11th Annual Concert, 1981 (Box 10, Reel 7-8)
      - 11th Annual Concert, 1981 (Box 15, Cassette 1-2)
    - 12th Annual Seminar, 1982
      - 12th Annual Concert, 1982 (Box 15, Cassette 3)
    - 13th Annual Seminar, 1983
      - Drums Workshop with Idris Muhammad | Brass Workshop with Woody Shaw, 1983 (Box 13, Cassette 1)
      - Percussion Workshop with Idris Muhammad | Piano Workshop with Kenny Barron | Guitar Workshop with Eric Gale, 1983 (Box 13, Cassette 2)
      - 13th Annual Concert, 1983 (Box 11, Reel 1-4)
    - 14th Annual Seminar, 1984
      - 14th Annual Concert, 1984 (Box 11, Reel 5-7)
      - 14th Annual Concert, 1984 (Box 15, Cassette 4)
    - 15th Annual Seminar, 1985
      - Bass Workshop with Rufus Reid, 1984 (Box 13, Cassette 3)
      - Drums Workshop with Idris Muhammad, 1985 (Box 13, Cassette 4)
      - Piano Workshop with Tommy Flannigan, 1985 (Box 13, Cassette 5)
      - Reeds Workshop with James Moody, 1985 (Box 13, Cassette 6-7)
      - 15th Annual Concert, 1985 (Box 11, Reel 8-9)
    - 16th Annual Seminar, 1986
      - Trumpet Workshop with Jon Faddis, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 8)
      - Drums Workshop with Akira Tana, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 9)
      - Guitar Workshop with John Scofield, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 10)
      - Piano Workshop with Joe Sample, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 11)
      - Music Synthesis Workshop with Randy Brecker, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 12)
      - Bass Workshop with Abraham Laboriel, 1986 (Box 13, Cassette 13)
      - 16th Annual Concert, 1986 (Box 12, Reel 1-3)
    - 17th Annual Seminar, 1977
      - Market Your Talent with George Butler and Guest Artist Harry Conic, 1987 (Box 13, Cassette 14)
      - 17th Annual Concert, 1987 (Box 12, Reel 4-8)
    - 18th Annual Seminar, 1988
      - Saxophone Workshop with Grover Washington, Jr., 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 15-16)
      - Drums Workshop with Billy Cobham, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 17)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Freddie Hubbard, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 18)
      - Workshop with Mike Hennesy-European Editor, Billboard Magazine, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 19)
      - Bass Workshop with Abraham Laboriel, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 20)
      - Piano Workshop with Monty Alexander, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 21)
      - 18th Annual Concert, 1988 (Box 15, Cassette 5-9)
      - 18th Annual Concert, 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 22-24)
    - 19th Annual Seminar, 1989
      - The State of Soviet Jazz, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 25)
      - Saxophone Workshop with Johnny Griffin, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 26)
      - Piano Workshop with Patrice Rushen, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 27)
      - Bass Workshop with Abraham Laboriel, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 28)
      - Drums Workshop with Idris Muhammad, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 29)
      - 19th Annual Concert, 1989 (Box 15, Cassette 10-11)
      - 19th Annual Concert, 1989 (Box 13, Cassette 30)
    - 20th Annual Seminar
      - Direct From Bombay: Jazz Critic Niranjan Jhaveri featuring Soloist D. Pandit, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 31)
      - The Business of Music with Paul Silverthorn: Attorney and Personal Manager for Grover Washington, Jr., 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 32)
      - Pittsburgh Jazz Orchestra with Special Guest Soloist Marcio Montarroyos, Direct from Rio de Janeiro, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 33)
      - Bass Workshop with Ray Drummond, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 34)
      - Saxophone Workshop with Grover Washington, Jr., 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 35)
      - Guitar Workshop with Kevin Eubanks, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 36)
      - Drums Workshop with Terri L. Carrington, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 37)
      - Flute Workshop with Herbie Mann, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 38)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Jon Faddis, 1990 (Box 13, Cassette 39)
      - 20th Annual Concert, 1990 (Box 15, Cassette 12-13)
    - 21st Annual Seminar, 1991
      - Inside the Music Business with Steve Backer and Ina Dittke, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 40)
      - Piano Workshop with Kenny Barron, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 41)
      - Bass Workshop with Ron Carter, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 42)
      - Guitar Workshop with Eric Gale, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 43)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Mike Mossman, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 44)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Arturo Sandoval, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 45)
      - Precussion Workshop with Alan Dawson, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 46)
      - Saxophone Workshop with Ernie Watts, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 47)
      - "The Expatriate Jazz Musician in Europe" with Ursula Davis, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 48)
      - "Music Medicine: Insights into the Physiological and Psychological Aspects of Performance" with Peter Wehling, 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 49)
      - 21st Annual Concert, 1991 (Box 15, Cassette 14-15)
      - "Such Sweet Thunder", 1991 (Box 15, Cassette 16-17)
      - Promo, 21st Annual Seminar and Concert, 1991 (Box 15, Cassette 28)
    - 22nd Annual Seminar, 1992
      - 22nd Annual Concert, 1992 (Box 15, Cassette 18-19)
    - 23rd Annual Seminar
      - Tenor Saxophone Workshop with Benny Golson, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 50)
      - Drums with Terri Lyne Carrington, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 51)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Randy Brecker, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 52)
      - Trombone Workshop with Curtis Fuller, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 53)
      - Guitar Workshop with Kevin Eubanks, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 54)
      - Composing and Arranging Workshop with Clare Fisher, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 55)
      - Inside the Music Business with Michele Adams and George Butler, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 56)
      - "Jazz in Eastern Europe" with Dionizy Piatkowski, 1993 (Box 13, Cassette 57)
    - 24th Annual Seminar, 1994
      - Production Master, 24th Annual Concert, 1994 (Box 15, Cassette 20-21)
      - 24th Annual Concert, 1994 (Box 15, Cassette 22-23)
    - 25th Annual Seminar, 1995
      - Music Production Workshop with Paul Silverthorn, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 58)
      - Reeds Workshops With James Moody and Grover Washington, Jr., 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 59)
      - Drums Workshop with Idris Muhammad, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 60)
      - Sound Engineering with Dae Bennett, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 61)
      - Piano Workshop with Patrice Rushen, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 62)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Jon Faddis, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 63)
      - Bass Workshop with Abraham Laboriel, 1995 (Box 13, Cassette 64)
    - 26th Annual Seminar, 1996
      - Trumpet Workshop with Benny Bailey, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 65)
      - Bass Workshop with Abraham Laboriel, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 66)
      - Flute Workshop with Herbie Mann, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 67)
      - The Music Industry with Marvin Witofsky, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 68)
      - Piano Workshop with Mulgrew Miller, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 69)
      - Drums Workshop with T.S. Monk, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 70)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Wallace Roney, 1996 (Box 13, Cassette 71)
      - Production Master, 26th Annual Concert, 1996 (Box 15, Cassette 24-25)
      - 26th Annual Concert, 1996 (Box 15, Cassette 26-27)
    - 27th Annual Seminar, 1997
      - Tenor Saxophone Workshop with Ernie Watts, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 72)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Jimmy Owens, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 73)
      - Trumpet Workshop with Terumasa Hino, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 74)
      - Trombone Workshop with Curtis Fuller, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 75)
      - Inside the Music Industry with Boo Frazier, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 76)
      - Alto Saxophone Workshop with Jackie McLean, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 77)
      - Drums Workshop with Winard Harper, 1997 (Box 13, Cassette 78)
    - 28th Annual Seminar, 1998
      - Saxophone Colossus: The Saxophone in Jazz with Hank Crawford and James Moody, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 79)
      - World Beat: The Influences of Latin Rhythms in Jazz with Abraham Laboriel, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 80)
      - The Magic of Jazz: The Flute as a Solo Jazz Instrument with Herbie Mann, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 81)
      - Artistry and Rhythm: A History of Drums in Jazz with Idris Muhamad, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 82)
      - Business of Music with Dave Laing and Kellis Parker, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 83)
      - The World of Brass with Jon Faddis, Curtis Fuller, and Eddie Henderson, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 84)
      - Bridging the Gap: From Classical to Jazz with George Cables and Larry Coryell, 1998 (Box 13, Cassette 85)
    - 29th Annual Seminar, 1999
      - The Business of Jazz with Willard Jenkins, 1999 (Box 13, Cassette 86)
      - The History of Jazz with Dan Morgenstern, 1999 (Box 13, Cassette 87)
      - The Saxophone in Jazz with Grover Washington Jr. and James Moody, 1999 (Box 13, Cassette 88)
      - Tribute to Miles Davis: The Trumpet in Jazz with Wallace Roney and Mike Mossman, 1999 (Box 13, Cassette 89)
      - The Classics Meet the Blues with Russell Malone and Kenny Barron, 1999 (Box 13, Cassette 90)
  - Video Recordings, Pitt Jazz Seminar and Concert, 1974-1999; 2.
    - 4th Annual Seminar, 1974
      - Keyboard Workshop with Jaki Byard, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 1-3)
      - Guitar Workshop with Jim Hall, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 4-5)
      - Drums Workshop with Alan Dawson, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 6)
      - Reeds Workshop with Sonny Rollins, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 7-9)
    - 10th Annual Seminar, 1980
      - Bass Workshop with Ron Carter, 1980 (Box 14, Video 1)
    - 13th Annual Seminar, 1983
      - Guitar Workshop with Eric Gale, 1983 (Box 14, Video 2)
    - 16th Annual Seminar, 1986
      - State of Jazz and Jazz Criticism: An International Perspective, 1986 (Box 14, Video 3)